Guide to the Mary Johnson Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject files, 1970-2015; Series IV
  - United States interventions and war, 1994-2003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Useful flyers, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Veterans benefits, 2004-2009 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Vietnam, Circa 1975 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - War Resistor League, 1995-2004 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - We the People, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Welfare
    - Coalition to End Child Poverty in Connecticut, 2001-2007 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Fair Share budget, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Jobs and welfare, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Poverty, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Reform, 2000-12 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1992-2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Workers
    - Immigrant workers freedom, 2001-2003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Social Security, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Youth Leadership Program, Circa 1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Youth programs and resources, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Yale unions, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Protest signs and posters, 1980-2012; Series V
  This series consists of protest signs, posters, and fliers created by Johnson or others involved with her organizations or events. There are also posters and fliers advertising events in the New Haven area.
  Series V is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - General, Circa 1984 - Circa 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Community works of Connecticut, Circa 1991 - Circa 2012 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Greater New Haven Coalition for People
    - General, Circa 1980 - Circa 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Anti-war protests, 1995-2008 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Healthcare campaign, Circa 1992 - Circa 1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - International Workers Day, 1995-2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - New Haven events, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Additional material, 2017-; Accession 2018-M-0024
  Printed program booklet and five DVDs from the memorial service for Mary Johnson, October 1, 2017.
  The computer files are unprocessed and may contain sensitive information or be in a physical state that would prohibit use. Researchers wishing to request access should email mssa.assist@yale.edu. The request should outline the scope and purpose of the research project, why the researcher believes the material is relevant to their project, and contact information. If possible the request should also include a list of specific material of interest including collection, box, and folder numbers (or folder descriptions if folders are not numbered). The review may take several weeks.
  - Memorial service program, 2017-10-01 (Box 1)
  - Mary Johnson celebration part 1, 2017-10-01; 1 (Box 2)
  - Mary Johnson celebration part 2, 2017-10-01; 1 (Box 3)
  - Mary Johnson celebration part 3, 2017-10-01; 1 (Box 4)
  - Mary Johnson celebration part 4, 2017-10-01; 1 (Box 5)
  - Photograph slideshow, 2017-10-01; 1 (Box 6)